greatgamesexperiment.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy Policy on Great Games Experiment

## Privacy Policy

### About this Privacy Policy

Great Games Experiment and PushButton Labs both greatly value the privacy of customers, visitors, and users to and of this web site.  This document covers the types of personal information that is collected as a participator on this web site and the manner in which it is used.  PushButton Labs considers personal information to be all information that renders you, the participator, identifiable -- including name, email address, or any other information that is not made publicly available by the user.

This policy is part of and subject to the Terms of Service.  Through your use of this web site, you are consenting that you agree with terms outlined in both the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect

As a participator on this web site, there are several types of information that we collect in order to provide an enriched and functional experience for the user.

  * User-submitted Information -- When registering an account with the Great Games Experiment, you provide to us your name, email address, and a password.  Throughout your experience on this web site, you may continue to submit or upload personal information regarding opinions and comments on items.
  * Log Files -- As is the case with all web sites, the server on which Great Games Experiment resides contains automated processes that collect information sent from the web browsers of all site visitors.  This information may include, but is not limited to, browser type, pages viewed, referring sites, and Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses.  This information is used in various methods to analyze site trends and improve on site practices.
  * Cookies -- The web site sets cookies, parcels of text sent to and from the web server and stored on the user's machine to identify the unique user, used for authentication and analytics purposes.  Upon closing your browser, a persistent cookie will remain on your machine, storing data related to your login information if you voluntarily choose to have it do such.  The site also sets a session cookie, used during one visit to this web site.  Upon closing your browser, this session cookie will be destroyed.  This site is accessible with cookies disabled, however some features of the site may not work properly if you choose to do so.

### How We Use Information

  * Information you submit, including opinions and comments, is used by the Great Games Experiment to provide to visitors of the site features and functionality.
  * Personally identifiable information is used by PushButton Labs and PushButton Labs alone to evaluate and implement better design practices and site processes.
  * Cookies are used to provide convenience to site visitors, enabling "remember me" functionality on logins and user profile specific site participation.
  * Your name and email address will not be disclosed or used for any third-party commercial or marketing campaigns without provided consent from individuals registering an account under that corresponding name and email address.

### When Do We Disclose Information

  * Your name and email address will not be disclosed or used for any third-party commercial or marketing campaigns without provided consent from individuals registering an account under that corresponding name and email address.
  * We may release personal information in the good faith belief that doing such is necessary in order to comply with local, state, and federal laws, to enforce our Terms of Service, to take precaution against third party accusations or allegations concerning liability, to ensure the safety of the Great Game Experiment or any of its users.
  * With provided consent from the user, information may be disclosed to third parties for various purposes.

### Submission of Personally Identifiable Information

You may choose to use this site without providing personally identifiable information.  However, in doing such, you will not be able to use many of the site's features and functionality.  When submitting personally identifiable information, this web site uses reasonable protective authorization methods to verify the presented identity of the individual.

### Information Collected Concerning Children

Because you must be thirteen years of age or older, and must have parental consent if between the ages of thirteen and eighteen, to use the Great Games Experiment, this web site does not collect information about children.

### Conditions of Use

Upon visiting the Great Games Experiment, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and arbitration of disputes.
